Guide to the AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO, Washington State Labor Council records, 1935-1978; 1962-1976; 0450-003; 62.97 cubic feet 63 boxes
  - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, SERIES I
    - Subject Files, Subseries G
      - Elections, Sub-Subseries 19
        - Washington Democratic Council, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20/18)
        - Washington Electoral Reform Advisory Council, 1971 (Box-folder 20/19)
      - Election Laws and Processes - Redistricting, Sub-Subseries 20
        - Redistricting, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 20/20)
        - Prince (George N.) vs. Kramer (A. Ludlow), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 20/21-20/22)
      - Energy, Sub-Subseries 21
        - Atomic Energy Commission's Demonstration Plant (Liquid Metal Fast Breeder Reactor), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 20/23)
        - Energy Emergency, 1973 (Box-folder 20/24)
        - Hanford Nuclear Reactor, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 20/25)
      - Environment, Sub-Subseries 22
        - Air Pollution Control Administration, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 20/26)
        - Air Quality Coalition, 1970 (Box-folder 20/27)
        - Alpine Lakes, 1976 (Box-folder 20/28)
        - Clean Air for Washington, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 20/29)
        - Clean and Beautiful, Inc.
          - General Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 20/30-20/31)
          - Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 20/32)
        - DDT, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 21/1)
        - Environmental Issues, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 21/2)
        - Ground Water Areas, 1974 (Box-folder 21/3)
        - Intrastate Water Quality Standards, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 21/4)
        - Keep Washington Green Association, Inc., 1961-1970 (Box-folder 21/5-21/6)
        - National Hells Canyon Association, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 21/7)
        - Olympic National Park, 1976 (Box-folder 21/8)
        - Puget Sound Air Pollution Control Agency, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 21/9-21/10)
        - Second Bacon Siphon and Tunnel, 1976 (Box-folder 21/11)
        - Survey 70, 1970 (Box-folder 21/12)
        - Washington Water Pollution Control Commission, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 21/13)
        - Washington Environmental Council vs. Southcenter Shopping Center, 1971 (Box-folder 21/14)
        - Western Environmental Trade Association
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 21/15-21/16)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Fairs, Sub-Subseries 23
        - Washington State Trade and Convention Task Force, 1978 (Box-folder 21/18)
        - Western Washington Fair, 1951-1979 (Box-folder 21/19)
      - Food Processing and Inspection, Sub-Subseries 24
        - Dairy Products, 1969 (Box-folder 21/20)
        - Fish Inspection, 1969 (Box-folder 21/21)
        - Meat Inspection, 1969 (Box-folder 21/22)
      - Foreign Trade, Sub-Subseries 25
        - Foreign Trade
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 21/23)
          - Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 21/24-21/25)
        - Labor-Management Committee for Fair Foreign Competition
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 21/26)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 21/27)
          - Newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 21/28)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 21/29)
      - Forests and Forestry, Undated; Sub-Subseries 26 (Box-folder 21/30)
      - Gambling, Sub-Subseries 27
        - Gambling, 1974 (Box-folder 21/31)
        - Petitions to Legalize Gambling, 1970 (Box-folder 21/32)
      - Health and Medical, Sub-Subseries 28
        - Health and Medical
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 21/33)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 21/34)
          - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 21/35)
        - ALF-CIO Statements, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 22/1)
        - Chiropractic Services, 1972 (Box-folder 22/2)
        - Health Systems Agencies, 1977 (Box-folder 22/3)
        - Hospital and Medical Costs, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 22/4)
        - Malpractice and Professional Liability, 1975 (Box-folder 22/5)
        - Medicaid, 1966 (Box-folder 22/6)
        - Mental Health, 1974 (Box-folder 22/7)
        - Nursing Home Administrators, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 22/8)
        - Nursing Home Employees, 1976 (Box-folder 22/9)
        - Northern State Hospital, Closure of, 1971 (Box-folder 22/10)
        - Osteopathic Profession, 1964 (Box-folder 22/11)
        - Public Education on Health, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 22/12)
        - Public Health Service, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 22/13)
        - Radiological Technicians, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 22/14)
        - Washington Labor and Industries Department, Occupational Health Standards Committee., 1973 (Box-folder 22/15)
        - Washington State Inter-agency Council on Smoking and Health, 1974 (Box-folder 22/16)
        - Washington State Labor Council Statements, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 22/17)
        - Washington State Public Health Association, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 22/18)
      - Health and Medical - National Health Insurance, Sub-Subseries 29
        - National Health Insurance
          - General Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 22/19)
          - Miscellaneous, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 22/20)
        - AFL-CIO and Washington State Labor Council Statements, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 22/21)
        - United States Health, Education and Welfare Department, National Health Security Plans Hearing, October 1977 (Box-folder 22/22)
        - United States House, Ways and Means Committee, Health Subcommittee National Health Security Hearings, 1976 (Box-folder 22/23)
      - Health and Medical - Group Care Plans, Sub-Subseries 30
        - Group Health Association of American, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 22/24)
        - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 22/25)
        - Health Maintenance Organizations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 22/26)
        - Group Care Plans, 1964-1975 (Box-folder 22/27)
        - Licensing Standards for Health Maintenance Organizations, 1974 (Box-folder 22/28)
      - Health and Medical Programs - Dental, Sub-Subseries 31
        - Health and Medical Programs, Dental, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 22/29)
      - Industry, Sub-Subseries 32
        - Industry, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 22/30)
        - "Watchdog" Project, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22/31)
      - Insurance, Sub-Subseries 33
        - Washington Insurance Commissioner, 1962-1975 (Box-folder 22/32-22/33)
        - Washington Insurance Commissioner, Opposition to Auto Insurance Rates Hike, 1969 (Box-folder 22/34)
        - Washington Labor and Industries Department, Insurance Rate Hearings, 1967 (Box-folder 22/35)
      - Insurance, Commercial, Sub-Subseries 34
        - Insurance, Commercial, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 22/36)
        - AFL-CIO Statements, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 22/37)
        - Airplane Insurance, 1970 (Box-folder 22/38)
        - Automobile Insurance Reform
          - Testimony, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 22/39)
          - Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 23/1)
          - Miscellaneous, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 23/2)
        - Flood Insurance, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 23/3)
        - Homeowners' Insurance, 1970 (Box-folder 23/4)
        - "Mass Merchandizing" Hearing, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 23/5)
        - "No-Fault " Auto Insurance, 1971 (Box-folder 23/6)
        - Premium Finance Companies, 1972 (Box-folder 23/7)
        - Public Employees Mutual Casualty Company, 1970 (Box-folder 23/8)
        - Saskatchewan Automobile Insurance Act, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 23/9)
        - Washington Surveying and Rating Bureau, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 23/10)
        - Washington Surveying and Rating Bureau, Retail Store Employees Union, Local 1001 case, 1975 (Box-folder 23/11-23/12)
        - Wisconsin, Insurance Companies, Management Contracts Study, 1966 (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Insurance, Industrial, Sub-Subseries 35
        - Industrial Insurance
          - General Correspondence, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 23/14-23/22)
          - Financial Reports, 1971 (Box-folder 23/23)
          - Statements, 1974 (Box-folder 23/24-23/25)
          - Newsletters, 1970 (Box-folder 23/26)
          - Legislation, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 23/27-23/30)
          - Case Files (Claims), 1959-1972 (Box-folder 24/1-24/4)
          - Clippings, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 24/5)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 24/6-24/8)
        - Administration of State Funds, 1959-1971 (Box-folder 24/9)
        - American Association of State Compensation Insurance Funds
          - General Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 24/10)
          - Reports, 1975, 1978 (Box-folder 24/11)
          - Conference and Conventions, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 24/12)
          - Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 24/13)
        - Clogston, J. Scott, Injury Case, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 24/14)
        - Cost of Living Increases, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 24/15)
        - Disability Ratings for Workmen's Compensation Insurance
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/16)
          - Rules Manuals, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/17)
          - Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/18)
        - Protection of Radiation Workers, 1957-1971 (Box-folder 24/19)
        - Workmen's Compensation
          - General Correspondence, 1947-1965 (Box-folder 24/20-24/24)
          - Miscellaneous, 1947-1961 (Box-folder 24/25)
        - Workmen's Compensation Advisor's, Inc., 1973-1977 (Box-folder 24/26)
      - Insurance, Industrial, State Agencies, Department of Labor and Industries, Sub-Subseries 36
        - Washington Labor and Industries Department
          - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 24/27)
          - Case Files - Washington State School Directors Association vs. Washington Labor and Industries Department, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24/28)
          - Miscellaneous, 1957-1976 (Box-folder 24/29)
        - Actuarial Valuation of Reserve Funds, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 24/30)
        - Disability Insurance (Non-Industrial), 1949 (Box-folder 25/1)
        - Medical Aid Rules, November 25, 1968 (Box-folder 25/2)
        - Medical Fee Rate Hearings, 1965-1977 (Box-folder 25/3-25/10)
        - Self-Insurance Manager, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 25/11)
      - Insurance, Industrial, State Agencies, Appeal Board, Sub-Subseries 37
        - Washington Industrial Insurance Appeals Board
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 25/12)
          - Case Statistics, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 25/13-25/14)
          - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box-folder 25/15)
        - Appointments to the Board, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 25/16)
        - Annual Rate Reports, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 25/17)
        - Attorney Fees, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 25/18)
        - Clerical Claims, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 25/19)
        - Oyster Workers Hearing, 1964 (Box-folder 25/20)
        - Special Decisions, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 25/21)
        - Rating of Unspecified Permanent Partial Disabilities-hearing, 1970 (Box-folder 25/22)
        - Washington Legislature, Industrial Appeals Committee (Interim)
          - General Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 25/23)
          - Miscellaneous, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 25/24)
      - Labor, Sub-Subseries 38
        - Labor (General Correspondence), 1964-1971 (Box-folder 25/25)
        - Organizing, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 25/26)
      - Labor Day, Sub-Subseries 39
        - Labor Day
          - General Correspondence, 1952-1977 (Box-folder 25/27-25/29)
          - Statements, AFL-CIO, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 25/30)
          - News Releases, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 25/31)
          - Miscellaneous, 1951-1969 (Box-folder 25/32)
        - Union Label Week
          - General Correspondence and Statements, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 25/33)
          - Miscellaneous, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 25/34)
      - Labor Law, Sub-Subseries 40
        - AFL-CIO, Labor Law Reform Task Force
          - General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26/1-26/2)
          - Newsletters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26/3)
          - Ephemera, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26/4)
          - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26/5)
      - Labor Disputes, Sub-Subseries 41
        - Allied Kingsport Press Unions vs. Kingsport Press, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 26/6)
        - AFL-CIO Policy, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 26/7)
        - AFL-CIO Policy vs. General Electric
          - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 26/8)
          - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box-folder 26/9)
        - Central Labor Council King County vs. Governor Albert Rosellini (Unfair List)
          - General Correspondence, 1962 (Box-folder 26/10)
          - Clippings, 1962 (Box-folder 26/11)
          - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 26/12)
        - Coalition for Protective Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 26/13)
        - Compulsory Arbitration, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 26/14)
        - Farah Slacks Boycott
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 26/15)
          - Newsletters, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 26/16)
          - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 26/17)
        - Farah Strikers Holiday Fund, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 26/18)
        - Financial Institution Employees of American, AFL-CIO, Local 1182, 1978 (Box-folder 26/19)
        - Machinists vs. National Airlines, 1970 (Box-folder 26/20)
        - National Railway Labor Dispute, 1967 (Box-folder 26/21)
        - Newspaper Guild vs. Herald Examiner, Los Angeles, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 26/22)
        - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers vs. Major Oil Companies, 1969, 1973 (Box-folder 26/23)
        - Protest of Extension Service Bulletin, "Labor Unions Are Headed for Your Farm", 1970 (Box-folder 26/24)
        - Protest Regarding Media Coverage of Nonferrous Metal Strike, 1968 (Box-folder 26/25)
        - Seattle Olympic Hotel Co. vs. WSLC, 1972 (Box-folder 26/26)
        - Service and Hospital Employees Union, Local 399 vs. United States, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 26/27)
        - Strawberry Pickers, 1974 (Box-folder 26/28)
        - United Farm Workers of California Grape Boycott
          - General Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 26/29-26/30)
          - Ephemera, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 26/31)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 26/32)
        - United Farm Workers of California vs. Lettuce Growers
          - General Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 27/1)
          - Reports and Statements, 1973-1975, Undated (Box-folder 27/2)
          - Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 27/3)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 27/4)
        - "We do not Patronize" Lists, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 27/5)
        - Miscellaneous Disputes
          - General Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box-folder 27/6-27/7)
          - Related Papers, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 27/8)
      - Legal Services and Lawyers, Sub-Subseries 42
        - Pre-paid Legal Services
          - General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 27/9)
          - Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 27/10)
          - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 27/11)
      - Maritime Organizations, Sub-Subseries 43
        - Maritime Organizations, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 27/12)
        - Western Shipbuilders Association
          - General Correspondence, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 27/13)
          - Miscellaneous, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 27/14)
      - Newspapers and Journals, Sub-Subseries 44
        - Newspapers and Journals, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/15)
        - Labor Press Commendations, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 27/16)
      - Oil and Gas Resources and Industries, Sub-Subseries 45
        - Coal-Slurry Pipeline, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 27/17)
        - El Paso Natural Gas Company Divestiture Case
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 27/20)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 27/21)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 27/22)
        - Foothills Pipelines Limited and the Maple Leaf Project, 1976 (Box-folder 27/23)
        - Washington Natural Resources Department, Oil and Gas Conservation Committee
          - General Correspondence, 1957-1972 (Box-folder 27/24)
          - Legislation, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 27/25)
      - Pension Plans, Sub-Subseries 46
        - Private Pension Plans, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/26)
        - Public Pension Plans, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 27/27)
      - Political Parties, Sub-Subseries 47
        - McGovern Commission on Party Structure, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 27/28)
        - Democratic Party, Washington State and County Central Committees
          - General Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 27/29)
          - Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 27/30)
      - Public Assistance, Sub-Subseries 48
        - Food Stamps and Food Surplus
          - General Correspondence, 1959-1972 (Box-folder 28/1)
          - Miscellaneous, circa 1970 (Box-folder 28/2)
        - Washington Public Assistance Department, 1961 (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Public Employees, Sub-Subseries 49
        - Public Employees
          - General Correspondence, 1958-1977 (Box-folder 28/4)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28/5)
          - Statements and Resolutions, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 28/6)
          - Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 28/7)
          - Miscellaneous, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 28/8)
        - Classified School District
          - Employees, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 28/9)
          - Health Service Employees, 1973 (Box-folder 28/10)
          - Pension, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 28/11)
          - Postal Employees, 1954-1970 (Box-folder 28/12)
          - Protection of Deputy Sheriffs' Civil Service, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 28/13)
          - Retired Public Employees Council of Washington and Public Employees Retirement System (PERS), 1971-1977 (Box-folder 28/14)
          - Service Employees International Union, Local 685, Doctors' Union, 1973 (Box-folder 28/15)
          - Teachers and Para-educational Personnel, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 28/16)
        - Washington Public Employees Relations Commission
          - General Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 28/17)
          - Legislation, 1975 (Box-folder 28/18)
          - Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 28/19)
      - Public Power, Sub-Subseries 50
        - Public Power
          - General Correspondence, 1958-1977 (Box-folder 28/20-28/23)
          - Minutes and Agenda, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 28/24)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1958-1969 (Box-folder 28/25)
          - Legislation, 1962 (Box-folder 28/26)
          - Maps and Charts, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 28/27)
          - Newsletters, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 28/28)
          - Miscellaneous, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 28/29)
        - American Public Power Association, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 28/30)
        - Little White Salmon Hydroelectric Project, 1964 (Box-folder 28/31)
        - Pacific Northwest Utilities Conference Commission, 1977 (Box-folder 28/32)
        - Public Utilities, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 28/33)
      - Sub-Subseries 51: Safety
        - Occupational and Industrial Safety
          - General Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 28/34-28/35)
          - Newsletters, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 28/36)
          - Legislation, 1965 (Box-folder 29/1)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 29/2)
        - Public Safety, 1971 (Box-folder 29/3)
        - Seattle-King County Safety Council, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 29/4)
        - Traffic Safety, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 29/5)
        - Washington Safety Council and Evergreen Safety Council, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29/6)
      - Scholarships, Sub-Subseries 52
        - Scholarships
          - General Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box-folder 29/7-29/16)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 29/17)
          - Photographs, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 29/18)
          - Miscellaneous, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 29/19)
      - Right-To-Work Laws, Sub-Subseries 53
        - Right-to-Work Laws
          - General Correspondence, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 29/20-29/24)
          - Reports, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 29/25)
          - Newsletters, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 29/26)
          - Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 29/27)
          - Ephemera, 1975 (Box-folder 29/28)
      - Senior Citizens, Sub-Subseries 54
        - Senior Citizens
          - General Correspondence, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 29/29)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 29/30)
        - AFL-CIO Committee on Older and Retired Persons, 1969 (Box-folder 29/31)
        - Concerned Seniors for Better Government, 1977 (Box-folder 29/32)
        - Elder Citizens' Coalition of Washington
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 29/33)
          - Miscellaneous, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 29/34)
        - United States Senate Committee on Aging (Special), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 29/35)
        - Washington Governor, Council on Aging
          - General Correspondence, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 29/36-29/37)
          - Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29/38)
      - Social Security, Sub-Subseries 55
        - Social Security, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 30/1)
      - Taxes - Federal, Sub-Subseries 56
        - Business and Corporate Taxes, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 30/2)
        - Federal Income Tax
          - General Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box-folder 30/3)
          - Statements and Reports, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 30/4)
        - Revenue Sharing
          - General Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 30/5)
          - Statements, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 30/6)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 30/7)
        - Severance Taxes, 1972 (Box-folder 30/8)
        - United States Federation of Taxpayers, 1966 (Box-folder 30/9)
        - Value Added Tax, 1972 (Box-folder 30/10)
      - Taxes - State, Sub-Subseries 57
        - State Taxes
          - General Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 30/11)
          - Speeches and Writings, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 30/12)
          - Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 30/13)
        - Arkansas Timber Tax Study, 1971 (Box-folder 30/14)
        - Miscellaneous Tax Facts, 1949-1975 (Box-folder 30/15)
        - Montana Tax Study, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 30/16)
        - Real Estate Excise Tax, 1965 (Box-folder 30/17)
        - Special School Levies, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 30/18)
        - State Income Tax, 1947-1977 (Box-folder 30/19)
        - Tax Reform
          - General Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 30/20)
          - Miscellaneous, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 30/21)
        - Washington State Tax Structure, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 30/22)
        - Washington Timber Tax
          - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 30/23)
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 30/24)
      - Telephone and Telegraph, Sub-Subseries 58
        - Pacific Northwest Bell, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 30/25)
        - Use of Telephone for Solicitations, 1964 (Box-folder 30/26)
      - Unemployment Compensation, Sub-Subseries 59
        - Unemployment Compensation
          - General Correspondence, 1950-1977 (Box-folder 30/27-30/36)
          - Statements, 1955-1976 (Box-folder 31/1)
          - Reports, 1956-1976 (Box-folder 31/2-31/4)
          - Rules and Regulations, 1956-1977 (Box-folder 31/5-31/6)
          - Legislation, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 31/7-31/8)
          - Hearings, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 31/9)
          - Newsletters, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 31/10)
          - Miscellaneous, 1963-1976 (Box-folder 31/11)
        - CETA (Comprehensive Employment Training Act), 1975-1978 (Box-folder 31/12)
        - Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of, Local 77 vs. Puget Power and Light Company, 1974 (Box-folder 31/13)
        - Farm Labor, 1971 (Box-folder 31/14)
        - Grain Millers, American Federation of, Local 86 vs. Fisher Mills, Inc.
          - General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 31/15)
          - Court Papers, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 31/16)
        - Paperworkers International Union, United vs. Inland Empire Paper Co., 1973-1974 (Box-folder 31/17)
        - J. C. Penney Company, 1975 (Box-folder 31/18)